DANIEL SHOAF

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

DETAILS

PHONE

760 623 5490

EMAIL

danielshoaf@gmail.com

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/danielshoaf/

LOCATION

San Diego, CA

EDUCATION

COLLEGE FOR CREATIVE STUDIES

Detroit, MI BFA Major in Illustration 2005-2009

SKILLS

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

ORGANIZATION

ATTENTION TO DETAIL

PROFILE

Experienced designer with over 6 years working in the apparel industry creating graphics, spot color separations, packaging, CADs, mock ups, and tech packs. I'm motivated by art and design and I strive to constantly be learning and improving skills. I enjoy working as part of a team, am open to taking direction, and able to work well under pressure.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

FOUR SEASONS DESIGN

2015 - Present San Diego, CA

- · Design graphic tees in a variety of styles
- Prepare art for print with spot color separation
- Packaging design for apparel and gifts
- Mock ups and colorways of gifts, accessories, and apparel
- Create CAD documents
- · Research fashion trends and present findings in meetings

GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN

COMMUNITY ALL STARS

2014 - 2015 San Diego, CA

- Created ads for businesses
- Designed posters and schedule cards for school sports teams